Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The Black Bulls are bound for the underwater temple and the magic stone coveted by the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Unfortunately, the powerful mana-driven currents that surround it prevent all from entering.
That mana weakens during a full moon, giving Noelle one week in which to master the spell that will allow underwater travel and help the magic knights reach the temple.
Noelle was discouraged by her inability to control her magic, but the mysterious girl Kahono, Asta, and the rest of the Black Bulls cheered her on until finally.
The Black Bulls accepted me. They relied on me. And now, I want to do something for them!
Water creation magic! Sea Dragon's Cradle!
Dragon's Cradle!
It...it...worked!
I see Dragon's Cradle! A new spell! Kahono! Did you see?
Huh? Where'd she go?
You've got great friends! In the end, they're the ones who should be here cheering you on. I'm glad it all worked out! Can't wait till the next time we meet, Noelle! I'll see you in the temple! Bye!
I'll see you in the next video!
Bye!
Well, tonight's the full moon. With the mana around here at its weakest, this is our best chance to get to the underwater temple.
So, you idiots ready to go?
Yeah! Just you wait, underwater temple!
Just you wait, magic stone!
Just you wait! Yummy seafood I never had anymore!
If I'm lucky, maybe they'll have some rare vintages to sample.
I wonder who we'll be up against down there! I hope they're strong! Come on, let's go already!
The sooner we go, the sooner we can return, and the sooner I can see Marie.
And then I can get back to the beach, babe!
Alright, I'm gonna go ahead and take that as a yes, then.
Okay, it looks like you're up!
What's wrong? You're not getting nervous, are you?
No way! It's not like there's anything for me to be nervous about!
I pulled it off fine yesterday!
Ha-ha! Easy, sweetie! Have a sip your stiffest aboard!
How about you not offer alcohol to the person we're trusting with our lives?!
When you're under a lot of pressure, things can go wrong, even if they've gone right a hundred times before.
Just remember, you gotta try and relax.
And if you do screw this up, I'm gonna kill you.
Oh yeah! No pressure at all!
Honestly, what is with them?
It almost feels silly to be nervous now.
I mean, really.
If my spell fails, we could all die!
But no one seems that worried about it.
Okay, here goes!
Water creation magic! Sea Dragon's Cradle!
Sea Dragon's Cradle!
Whoa!
I did it! I cast the spell!
Yeah, we knew you could do it!
But, uh...
We're a little squished here!
They're big enough without the floating thing!
Should I kill Gray?
Come on!
Transform into someone smaller!
Hey!
Well, Pions, is this better?
Now can we shrink the attitude?!
Not a bad job at all, Noelle.
Now you just gotta get us down to the underwater temple.
Right. I've got it covered.
Everybody, hang on tight!
He complimented me!
It's so cool!
It's almost like we're flying through the ocean!
Look at all those yucky fish begging to be to the deline!
Chica, look, Marie!
We're traveling under the water using magic!
Noelle, get us closer to those fish!
Marie wants to see them!
It doesn't work like that, moron!
No!
Come back!
I'm lost without the sight of your sweet face!
I can already feel the mana getting stronger down here!
Please!
What's that?!
It doesn't look good!
I'd say we've reached the strong magic region.
This is what it's like down here when the mana's at its weakest?!
Man, this strong magic region is something else!
This bubble thing isn't gonna pop on us, is it?!
You've gotta be pretty scared being a flame mage and all!
Please!
I don't know what you're talking about!
I've never been scared in my life!
Noelle!
She's our man and she can't do it!
Will you three be quiet please!
I'm trying to concentrate here!
I'm just barely avoiding all these currents!
It's almost like the mana is helping me!
This'll work!
I feel sick!
I think I'm gonna poo!
Don't even think about it, you wino!
The currents have let up a bit!
I feel sick!
I think I'm gonna poo!
Don't even think about it, you wino!
The currents have let up a bit!
It's beautiful.
They've sure got some funky looking animals down here.
Yeah, that fish is glowing like crazy.
Kinda looks like, yeah, it's magic, that's pretty cool.
Guess all this mana messed with the way the beasties around here
evolved.
Yeah, but do they taste any good?
Let's catch it and find out if its flavor has evolved, too!
Get over here, Windows!
Not so fast!
Are you two idiots seriously willing to die for a little food?
And Kray, we really don't need another bottomless pit around!
Hey, look!
Those whirlpools!
It's a magic barrier!
And an extremely powerful one!
My spell won't get us through it!
Okay, kid, you're up.
Give that thing a nice big slash with your sword.
Captain Yami?
Yeah?
The thing is, this was my first trip to the beach, and it taught me something really important.
I don't know how to swim!
Funny, huh?
You think I would've known before now, huh?
Good thing you won't need to swim.
Alright, you're probably gonna need to hold your breath for this.
I'm the captain here, so that means your pace is my pace.
And my pace is the pace, you got that?
Woohoo!
Ready?
And...
Ah!
Meteor!
I'm gonna drown!
Hold on.
Oh hey, I can breathe.
Thanks, kid.
I can't believe we didn't die!
See, I knew you were scared.
Who even wet yourself?
Shut up, Lightning Boy!
Let's just see water and you know it!
The mana's too strong here for me to get a hold of Marie.
Goosh!
Hey, Goosh!
Huh?
You're kinda standing on me!
You think I care?
Well, this is nice.
Crazy, something like this exists at the bottom of the ocean.
Whoa!
So that's the underwater temple!
Charmy, whip us up some cotton.
Roger!
What's up?
Absolutely!
Thank you!
Well, this is a bust.
We haven't even been attacked once!
He's right.
There don't seem to be any trap spells.
I expected something.
Yawn.
This is getting tedious.
You'd better not be letting your guard down, you hear me?
There's nothing safe about a strong magic region, so get yourselves fired up!
Yes, sir!
attacked once he's right there don't seem to be any trap spells i expected something yawn
this is getting tedious you had better not be letting your guard down you hear me
there's nothing safe about a strong magic region so get yourselves fired up yes sir
whoa
this is awesome are these houses that means there are probably ocean folk down here are
they strong and scary and super powerful i can't wait to fight them well that makes one of us at
least look people luck was right ocean folk they're not gonna attack us are they don't hear you
whoa look over there hey oh yeah i think they heard you
you don't see that every day we've got real live visitors and if the robes are anything to go by it
looks like they're magic knights cute ones too please tell us about the outside world so have you been
sent out on any dangerous missions lately must have been ten years since we had visitors here hey i was
picturing someplace a whole lot scarier and more dungeon-y with booby traps and tricky magic hate to
break it to you but imagination doesn't really tend to match reality we had to look around for someone
who knows about that magic stone right captain i'm on it i want to talk to whoever's the boss of this
temple okay maybe we should ask a little more nicely sir yeah no problem that would be the high priest
you're looking for kay he's way up at the top of those stairs so i hope you don't mind a bit of a hike
kay i can take you there if you want kay they started a trend you should join us for a beach
barbecue later you are such a cutie isn't she gauche please marie's a billion times cuter
come on gray transform into me and we can get some twin action going
hitting on girls while looking like gordon why him of all people
so far this has been a lot easier than i expected it to be well i'm not complaining
but how will you cope without your regularly scheduled near-death experience hey it's not
like i go around asking people to try and kill me well here we are
making sure and tell the high priest hello for us okay we'll talk more about the outside world when
you come back yeah and thank you well good luck don't thank us yet
look someone's here think that's the high priest guy we're looking for hey
whoops
oh
A huge fish!
What's he?
I'll stop poking with your sword or something!
Maybe it's actually a kind of temple garden!
And it only looks ugly and terrifying!
We should wait until it attacks!
That ought to do it!
What was that thing anyway?
You guys didn't waste any time!
Oh, this is wonderful!
I love it when we have exciting visitors!
Ha! Yes, welcome to the underwater temple!
I'm the high priest of this subaqueous structure!
Wait, this freaky geezer is the one in charge here?
That wasn't the most neighborly welcome you gave us, you old fart.
I can't tell you how much I enjoy catching people off guard like that!
Did you see how they reacted?
Delightful!
This guy needs a new hobby!
Do you taste good?
Easy there, Charmy.
I'd leave the monster thing alone if I were you.
It's all sliced up!
Like it wants me to eat it!
Sorry kids, you can't eat magic.
I didn't even get one bite!
What kind of magic was he using?
It's not easy to make something that enormous.
This guy must be really powerful.
You came to my temple to seek the magic stone, didn't you?
If you want it, you'll have to play a game with me first!
Huh?
What kind of game are we talking about?
Here we go.
I can tell this guy is trouble.
He'll act like it's just for fun, right up until we lose and he kills us all!
Well, are you ready?
The name of this little game is...
Find out how squishy the boobs are!
How about we play this game instead?
Hey, you can't go beating up the high priest!
He's still got a big shot!
So what? I'm royalty!
It was just a joke.
Well, now I'm going to show you exactly how not funny I think that kind of joke is!
I really don't think that's a good idea, Noelle!
Alright, enough messing around.
We didn't drag our butts all the way out here to play games with you.
How'd you know we were after the magic stone, anyway?
You'd be surprised how well these old eyes still see.
So what are you going to do?
Your kingdom needs that stone, doesn't it?
What do you think? Beat him up and take it by force?
Yeah, that would probably be the fastest.
It looks like the geys are super powerful, so fighting him would get my vote for sure!
What kind of twisted stuff are you three plotting over here?!
Beating up old men isn't what the magic knights are about?!
I'm telling you, that's no ordinary old man.
We don't want to get caught up with someone like him.
Do you think we have time to take a nap?
Forget napping, I want to know when dinner is!
Is it you three even care at all?!
Aw, haven't you made up your minds yet?
Play with me and not only will you get the magic stone,
but I'll round up the temple's loveliest ladies, finest drinks, and tastiest food!
We'll have a magnificent banquet!
What do you think?
Shall we play?
Yeah, let's do it!
Is that seriously what's more important to you?!
I'll play the game because of our mission, not some stupid party!
Woo-hoo!
That's enough out of you.
Looks like we got no choice.
Alright then, old man.
You want to play so bad, take on this master gambler.
Go get him!
No one cannot play you, Captain Yummy!
Okay, so what game is it gonna be?
Dice?
Roulette?
Woo-hoo!
A brawl!
A real temple battle royal!
Yeah!
Temple mages!
Come on down!
King magic!
It's time for Temple Shuffle!
What the?
Looks like more doors.
You summoned us, high priest?
Finally, mages from the outside have come to visit us.
Oh, this is going to be fun.
I'm not sure.
They don't seem as impressive as we thought.
But you're talking fast.
Come on.
Those are the lamest masks I've ever seen.
Oh, this is bad.
I'm sensing a ton of power here.
Are these mages temple warriors?
All righty.
Shall we get started?
Like, no?
What exactly are we starting?
Are you ready?
Okay.
Let's go.
We're totally not ready.
Okay.
What the heck?
Where am I? Where's everyone else?
Testing, testing, can you all hear me?
As you may have noticed, you've been separated and placed in various spots throughout the temple.
This is inside the temple?
You saw the temple ages a short while ago.
How come the community's dressed?
Who's the thing?
Wait, I never actually learned any attack magic.
How is it that I'm just realizing this now?
Hold on.
Did he say it was going to be a nine-on-nine battle?
But there should be ten of us.
The rules are very simple.
Knock them out and you win.
Make them surrender and you win.
Well, I'm a little bit more awake now, at least.
All the one with the most players left standing when the game concludes will be the winner.
I just want to do that skill crap.
You may play any way you like.
Fight one-on-one, hide and hope to outlast the others,
find friends men together and swarm the enemy.
The choice is yours.
What kind of vicious game is this?
That's it.
I'm out of here.
Good luck, guys.
Just make sure you keep an eye out for my nuisance spells.
They can be a bit startled.
Nuisance spells.
I'll show you a nuisance, old man.
Oh, yeah.
I'm so there.
This is going to be a total bloodbath.
All right.
I got it.
Now let's go.
I'm ready.
What's this?
How interesting.
I'm not sensing so much as a scrap of magic coming from you.
Tell me, can you even fight?
Too bad.
I was hoping for a good opponent, but it looks like I got a dud.
You think I'm a dud, huh?
Just try me and find out.
For a young and a morning
どうして眠れない
こんなバッテイバイバイブラックバース
つぶやいても消えない強い不安
For hours lately
I've been crying for hours, baby
I wish you were here
君がくれた
All those letters
読み返すたびに
The pain's gone
一人じゃない
Cause we're a perfecter sport
離れば何でも
繋がる
Believe in you
いつもそばに
感じているから
Fore a side of me
And I'll go before you
君に行こう
You know you're not alone
Cause we're a perfecter sport
離れば何でも
繋がる
You're within me
いつもそばに
私がいるから
Fore a side of me
And I'll go before you
君に行こう
Fore a side of me
I'm sorry to call
The nine of you
Here like this
However
There is an urgent matter
That I needed to discuss
With you
Huh
Wait a minute
Now that you're all
Standing here
I sense that
Something's amiss
There's one too many
One too many
Too many of what
Of you
There should only be nine
What
This is unbelievable
There's an imposter
Among the ranks
Of the temple mages
Huh
What
Is there something wrong
Yeah
I'd say there is
You're not exactly
A sea creature
Oh I get it
You're messing with me
And what's your favorite food
Peanuts of course
And what's your best feature
My long nose of course
And what does that make you
An elephant
I'm an elephant
Have you ever tried a peanut
No
You sure get a legend
Really
Welcome to the Underwater temple
I know what you're after
If you want the magic stone
You'd better be ready to fight for it
Black Clover page 43
Temple Battle Royale
Yeah that's right
I'm the high priest here
I'm kind of a big deal
exc indicating your favorite talk
ifications of this
I'm done
So
iman
I
Among the
B прys
I'm
You're
E